GMT-5 | (+51) 961261925 | vdanfel@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/victor-felipa Chinchaysuyo 243 Carabayllo, 15318, Lima Nationality: peruvian | DNI: 45586417

Professional Summary

Programmer with 10 years of experience in back-end development (C#, .NET, SQL Server). In 2023, transitioned to Full Stack, emphasizing .NET Core 6, JavaScript, and JSON. Specialized in building dynamic pages using MVC and Razor, integrating front-end technologies like HTML5, CSS, and Bootstrap. Focused on efficient solutions and communicative, with a track record of effective teamwork and attention to user and client needs.

Professional Experience

NEXTEPPE – Full Stack Developer

Feb 2024 - Apr 2024

New York Company with 15 years of experience, specializing in automotive inventory.

- Updated legacy code to modern versions, resulting in improved API performance.
- Developed the settings page for the client's website (search page and details page).
- Developed search page with advanced filters.
- Developed details page.
- Provided ongoing user support, ensuring smooth and satisfactory flow in implemented systems.

Technological Stack: C#, ASP.Net, MVC, Json, JavaScript, Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS.

NORLIMA – Full Stack Programmer

Jul 2023 - Dec 2023

Leading company with 27 years of expertise in the production and commercialization of bricks for construction.

- Developed a new system for employee time tracking and access control, enhancing the workflow and addressing various scenarios (Regular Attendance, Hourly Permits, and Overtime). Reduced report handling time from 10 to 5 minutes, improving calculations for the Human Resources department.
- Created a new system for mealtime tracking, enhancing payment reports to the cafeteria and reducing review time from 1 hour to 10 minutes.
- Updated windows, workflows, and processes, introducing improvements and new features based on the needs of different departments, particularly in Human Resources and Logistics.
- Led the development of a new service provider portal, reducing the validation time for personnel entering the plant from 1 week to 2 days. Managed the entire process from documentation to on-site registration.
- Provided ongoing user support, ensuring an efficient and satisfactory flow in the implemented systems.

Technological Stack: C#, ASP.Net, MVC, Net Core 6, Json, JavaScript, Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS.

CASSINELLI – Back end Programmer

Oct 2018 - Jan 2023

Retail company part of the CELIMA TREBOL group focused on sectors A and B, specialized in the marketing of national and international home finishing products.

- Reduced the creation time of bulk Purchase Orders (OC) from 5 days to 1 day by automating the review, separation, and loading process.
- Streamlined the creation of accounting entries, reducing time and personnel, by automating the sales flow and accounting reports.
- Enhanced user response by 30% for reported issues; developed a web-based helpdesk system.
- Decreased the time for creating reports requested by store administrators to view sales reports from 10 minutes to 3 minutes.
- Improved the time and attendance system by updating the internal web application with front-end applications.
- Automated processes for store creations, reducing the creation time from 2 days to 3 hours.

Technological Stack: C#, ASP.Net, MVC, SOLID, MSSQL, ETL, Power BI, CSS, HTML, Bootstrap, JQuery, Web APIs, Centura Builder.

CASSINELLI – Support Analyst

Jun 2016 - Sep 2018

- Modified network structure, improving data traffic by 30%.
- Contributed to the Active Directory restructuring project.
- Analyzed, diagnosed, repaired, and replaced defective or damaged hardware components, achieving a recovery of 10-25% of the cost of discarded equipment.
- Conducted analysis and diagnosis of failures in equipment, systems, and networks.
- Managed and tracked support requests until resolution.
- Provided remote or on-site user support.

Technological Sack: Windows Server, CCNA, Topología de Redes, Active Directory, IIS, VMWare.

CENTRO CERAMICO LAS FLORES - IT Assistant

May 2015 - Jun 2016

Retail company part of the CELIMA TREBOL group focused on sectors A and B, specialized in the marketing of national and international home finishing products.

- Increased sales by 25% by developing a room simulator using asp.net C# and SQL Server, streamlining interaction between sellers and end consumers.
- Reduced report visualization time from 5 to 2 minutes using Qlikview to create new managerial dashboards.
- Decreased store creation time in the system from 40 to 10 minutes by automating manual processes through query creation.
- Automated test processes from 60 to 5 minutes by creating queries for the swift creation of clients, users, and providers.

Technological Stack: C#, ASP.Net, MVC, SQL Server, SAP, QlikView.

CENTRO CERAMICO LAS FLORES – System Intern

Mar 2014 - Apr 2015

- Improved shared folder distribution by 60% through domain server updates, enhancing access distribution via Active Directory.
- Provided remote or on-site user support.
- Responsible for aiding in the improvement of server, network, and database administration and maintenance.

Technological Stack: PHP, SQL Server, C#, ASP.Net, SAP, CCNA, Topología de redes

Freelance Programmer

Jan 2016 - Present

• INMOBILIRIA TAIPE 2023: Migration of the desktop system to a web environment, achieving real-time visualization of debtors and separate lot information.

- INMOBILIRIA TAIPE 2018: Developed software to automate manual processes for client registration and lot sales, reducing search time for client Kardex from 15 to 1 min, creation of payment vouchers from 10 to 1 min, client registration from 10 to 2 min, and contract preparation from 5 to 1 min.
- ACINMAG 2017: Created a website to showcase products, resulting in a 30% increase in sales.
- CLAMATE 2017: Developed a web-based game for patient interviews, reducing evaluation time from 30 to 10 min and result review time from 15 to 1 min.
- TRAVIAMAR 2016: Created a news manager using C#, ASP.Net, and SQL, increasing news publication speed by 60%.

Education

Cesar Vallejo University – Bachelor's Degree in Systems Engineering – 2008-2018

Skills

- Programming Languages: <u>Advanced:</u> C#, ASP.Net, Net Core 6, HTML5, CSS. | <u>Intermediate:</u> Bootstrap, Centura. | <u>Basic:</u> JavaScript, Json.
- Framework Tools: <u>Advanced:</u> Visual Studio, SQL Management, Centura Builder. | <u>Intermediate:</u> Unity HUB.
- Database: Advanced: SQL Server. | Intermediate: MySQL. | Basic: Oracle.
- Tools: Intermediate: BitBucket, Git, Slack.
- Methodologies: Advanced: Iconix. | Intermediate: SCRUM. | Basic: RUP.
- Microsoft: Advanced: Excel, Word. | Intermediate: Power Point, Visio, Project.

Languages

English: A2-B1. Spanish: Native.

Cursos y Especializaciones

| UDEMY | |
|--|------|
| - JavaScript TOTAL - From Zero to Web Developer in 18 Days (In Progress) | 2024 |
| - C# TOTAL - Expert Programmer in 28 Days (In Progress) | 2024 |
| - Building RESTful Web APIs with ASP.NET Core 6 (Completed) | 2024 |
| - Microservices with ASP.NET Core, Docker, and RabbitMQ (Completed) | 2023 |
| - Learn ASP.NET Core MVC 6 by Building Projects from Scratch (Completed) | 2023 |
| Master in Video Game Programming with Unity® 2021 and C# (Completed) | 2023 |
| - RESTful Web Services REST APIs: From Zero to Expert (Completed) | 2022 |
| - SQL Server: Advanced Programming 2021 (Completed) | 2021 |
| - SAP ABAP Programming Introduction (Completed) | 2018 |
| Unreal Engine from Scratch: Create 3 Games with Blueprints and C++ (Completed) | 2018 |
| CESAR VALLEJO UNIVERSITY | |
| - CCNA3. (Completed) | 2014 |
| - Linux Configuration. (Completed) | 2014 |
| - C++ and Visual Studio. (Completed) | 2011 |
| UNI SYSTEMS | |
| - Dream Weaver – BD / Fireworks (Update). (Completed) | 2013 |
| - Dream Weaver – BD / Fireworks. (Completed) | 2012 |
| - Basic Dream Weaver. (Completed) | 2012 |
| - Algorithms and Data Structures. (Completed) | 2011 |
| - PC Devices and Utilities Configuration. (Completed) | 2008 |
| - Maintenance and Diagnostics. (Completed) | 2008 |
| - PC Repair. (Completed) | 2008 |
| - PC Assembly. (Completed) | 2008 |
| - Connectivity and Structured Cabling. (Completed) | 2008 |
| - Hardware and Networks Expert. (Completed) | 2008 |
| | |

AVAILABILITY: IMMEDIATE